{"success": 1, "total": 2100, "result": [{"ID": "55e429cfe4b0152a610c8336", "typeID": "54993f56e4b06783458c3b0f", "optionD": "None of the above.", "optionC": "Multiple threads mar cause deadlock,while multiple processes won't cause deadlock.", "optionAnswer": "B", "answer": "B\u662f\u5bf9\u7684\uff0cAC\u90fd\u6709\u9519", "optionB": "Changes to the main thread(cancellation\uff0cpriority change\uff0cetc.) may affect the behavior of the other threads of the process; Changes to the parent process does not affect child processes.", "type": "1", "optionA": "Threads share the same address space of the parent process;Processes share the same address space of the parent process.", "knowledge": "\u7ebf\u7a0b", "question": "Which statement(s) is(are) correct about thread and process\uff1f", "title": "Microsoft-2014\u6821\u56ed\u62db\u8058\u7b14\u8bd5\u9898"}, {"ID": "55e429cfe4b0152a610c8337", "typeID": "54993f56e4b06783458c3b0f", "optionD": "None of the above", "optionC": "Port numbers below 1024 are called well-known ports and are reserved for standard services. For example,port 21 is reserved for FTP protocol, and port 25 is for SMTP protocol.", "optionAnswer": "C", "answer": "C\u662f\u6b63\u786e\u7684", "optionB": "TCP supports multicasting.", "type": "1", "optionA": "TCP provides a way for applications to send encapsulated IP datagrams and send them without having to establish a connection.", "knowledge": "\u7f51\u7edc", "question": "Which statement(s) below regarding TCP(Transmission Control Protocol) is(are) correct?", "title": "Microsoft-2014\u6821\u56ed\u62db\u8058\u7b14\u8bd5\u9898"}, {"ID": "55e429cfe4b0152a610c8338", "typeID": "54993f56e4b06783458c3b0f", "optionD": "DES", "optionC": "RC4", "optionAnswer": "A", "answer": "MD5\u662f\u4e0d\u53ef\u9006\u52a0\u5bc6\uff0c\u4e0d\u53ef\u4ee5\u7528\u6765\u52a0\u5bc6\u6587\u672c\uff0cDES\u548cRC4\u662f\u5bf9\u79f0\u52a0\u5bc6\uff0cRSA\u662f\u4e0d\u5bf9\u79f0\u52a0\u5bc6\uff0c\u90fd\u53ef\u4ee5\u7528\u4e8e\u6587\u672c\u52a0\u5bc6\u3002", "optionB": "RSA", "type": "1", "optionA": "MD5", "knowledge": "\u52a0\u5bc6", "question": "Which of the following method(s) CANNOT be used for Text-encryption:", "title": "Microsoft-2014\u6821\u56ed\u62db\u8058\u7b14\u8bd5\u9898"}, {"ID": "55e429cfe4b0152a610c8339", "typeID": "54993f56e4b06783458c3b0f", "optionD": "Many clustered index", "optionC": "clustered index and many non-clustered indexes", "optionAnswer": "D", "answer": "\u4e00\u5f20\u8868\u4e0d\u80fd\u6709\u591a\u4e2a\u4e1b\u805a\u7d22\u5f15", "optionB": "A clustered index", "type": "1", "optionA": "No indexes", "knowledge": "\u6570\u636e\u5e93", "question": "A table CANNOT have one or more of the following index configurations.", "title": "Microsoft-2014\u6821\u56ed\u62db\u8058\u7b14\u8bd5\u9898"}, {"ID": "55e429cfe4b0152a610c833a", "typeID": "54993f56e4b06783458c3b0f", "optionD": "1", "optionC": "0", "optionAnswer": "B", "answer": "\u8fd0\u884c\u53ef\u77e5", "optionB": "-1", "type": "1", "optionA": "-2", "knowledge": "\u7f16\u7a0b\u57fa\u7840", "question": "Initialize integer i as 0, what's the value of i after the following operation?  i += i > 0 ? i++ : i --;  ", "title": "Microsoft-2014\u6821\u56ed\u62db\u8058\u7b14\u8bd5\u9898"}, {"ID": "55e429cfe4b0152a610c833b", "typeID": "54993f56e4b06783458c3b0f", "optionD": "BSS segment", "optionC": "global variable", "optionAnswer": "A", "answer": "\u9009A", "optionB": "static variable", "type": "1", "optionA": "code segment", "knowledge": "\u8fdb\u7a0b", "question": "When a dll is loaded into memory, which part(s) can be shared between processes", "title": "Microsoft-2014\u6821\u56ed\u62db\u8058\u7b14\u8bd5\u9898"}, {"ID": "55e429cfe4b0152a610c833c", "typeID": "54993f56e4b06783458c3b0f", "optionD": "O(n*n)", "optionC": "O(nlgn)", "optionAnswer": "C", "answer": "\u5feb\u6392\u7684\u590d\u6742\u5ea6\u4e3aC", "optionB": "O(n)", "type": "1", "optionA": "O(lgn)", "knowledge": "\u590d\u6742\u5ea6", "question": "The best time complexity of quick sort algorithm is:", "title": "Microsoft-2014\u6821\u56ed\u62db\u8058\u7b14\u8bd5\u9898"}, {"ID": "55f2dfa6e4b0152a61142e2a", "typeID": "54993f56e4b06783458c3b0f", "optionD": "None of the above.", "optionC": "Multiple threads mar cause deadlock,while multiple processes won't cause deadlock.", "optionAnswer": "B", "answer": "B\u662f\u5bf9\u7684\uff0cAC\u90fd\u6709\u9519", "optionB": "Changes to the main thread(cancellation\uff0cpriority change\uff0cetc.) may affect the behavior of the other threads of the process; Changes to the parent process does not affect child processes.", "type": "1", "optionA": "Threads share the same address space of the parent process;Processes share the same address space of the parent process.", "knowledge": "\u7ebf\u7a0b", "question": "Which statement(s) is(are) correct about thread and process\uff1f", "title": "Microsoft-2014\u6821\u56ed\u62db\u8058\u7b14\u8bd5\u9898"}, {"ID": "55f2dfa6e4b0152a61142e2b", "typeID": "54993f56e4b06783458c3b0f", "optionD": "None of the above", "optionC": "Port numbers below 1024 are called well-known ports and are reserved for standard services. For example,port 21 is reserved for FTP protocol, and port 25 is for SMTP protocol.", "optionAnswer": "C", "answer": "C\u662f\u6b63\u786e\u7684", "optionB": "TCP supports multicasting.", "type": "1", "optionA": "TCP provides a way for applications to send encapsulated IP datagrams and send them without having to establish a connection.", "knowledge": "\u7f51\u7edc", "question": "Which statement(s) below regarding TCP(Transmission Control Protocol) is(are) correct?", "title": "Microsoft-2014\u6821\u56ed\u62db\u8058\u7b14\u8bd5\u9898"}, {"ID": "55f2dfa6e4b0152a61142e2c", "typeID": "54993f56e4b06783458c3b0f", "optionD": "DES", "optionC": "RC4", "optionAnswer": "A", "answer": "MD5\u662f\u4e0d\u53ef\u9006\u52a0\u5bc6\uff0c\u4e0d\u53ef\u4ee5\u7528\u6765\u52a0\u5bc6\u6587\u672c\uff0cDES\u548cRC4\u662f\u5bf9\u79f0\u52a0\u5bc6\uff0cRSA\u662f\u4e0d\u5bf9\u79f0\u52a0\u5bc6\uff0c\u90fd\u53ef\u4ee5\u7528\u4e8e\u6587\u672c\u52a0\u5bc6\u3002", "optionB": "RSA", "type": "1", "optionA": "MD5", "knowledge": "\u52a0\u5bc6", "question": "Which of the following method(s) CANNOT be used for Text-encryption:", "title": "Microsoft-2014\u6821\u56ed\u62db\u8058\u7b14\u8bd5\u9898"}, {"ID": "55f2dfa6e4b0152a61142e2d", "typeID": "54993f56e4b06783458c3b0f", "optionD": "Many clustered index", "optionC": "clustered index and many non-clustered indexes", "optionAnswer": "D", "answer": "\u4e00\u5f20\u8868\u4e0d\u80fd\u6709\u591a\u4e2a\u4e1b\u805a\u7d22\u5f15", "optionB": "A clustered index", "type": "1", "optionA": "No indexes", "knowledge": "\u6570\u636e\u5e93", "question": "A table CANNOT have one or more of the following index configurations.", "title": "Microsoft-2014\u6821\u56ed\u62db\u8058\u7b14\u8bd5\u9898"}, {"ID": "55f2dfa6e4b0152a61142e2e", "typeID": "54993f56e4b06783458c3b0f", "optionD": "1", "optionC": "0", "optionAnswer": "B", "answer": "\u8fd0\u884c\u53ef\u77e5", "optionB": "-1", "type": "1", "optionA": "-2", "knowledge": "\u7f16\u7a0b\u57fa\u7840", "question": "Initialize integer i as 0, what's the value of i after the following operation?  i += i > 0 ? i++ : i --;  ", "title": "Microsoft-2014\u6821\u56ed\u62db\u8058\u7b14\u8bd5\u9898"}, {"ID": "55fa6a5ce4b043d0caf27234", "typeID": "55dd5e2360b258078b9e4458", "optionD": "None of the above.", "optionC": "Multiple threads mar cause deadlock,while multiple processes won't cause deadlock.", "optionAnswer": "B", "answer": " ", "optionB": "Changes to the main thread(cancellation\uff0cpriority change\uff0cetc.) may affect the behavior of the other threads of the process; Changes to the parent process does not affect child processes.", "type": "1", "optionA": "Threads share the same address space of the parent process;Processes share the same address space of the parent process.", "knowledge": "\u7ebf\u7a0b", "question": "Which statement(s) is(are) correct about thread and process\uff1f", "title": "Microsoft-2014\u6821\u56ed\u62db\u8058\u7b14\u8bd5\u9898"}, {"ID": "55fa6a5ce4b043d0caf27235", "typeID": "55dd5e2360b258078b9e4458", "optionD": "None of the above", "optionC": "Port numbers below 1024 are called well-known ports and are reserved for standard services. For example,port 21 is reserved for FTP protocol, and port 25 is for SMTP protocol.", "optionAnswer": "C", "answer": " ", "optionB": "TCP supports multicasting.", "type": "1", "optionA": "TCP provides a way for applications to send encapsulated IP datagrams and send them without having to establish a connection.", "knowledge": "\u7f51\u7edc", "question": "Which statement(s) below regarding TCP(Transmission Control Protocol) is(are) correct?", "title": "Microsoft-2014\u6821\u56ed\u62db\u8058\u7b14\u8bd5\u9898"}, {"ID": "55fa6a5ce4b043d0caf27236", "typeID": "55dd5e2360b258078b9e4458", "optionD": "DES", "optionC": "RC4", "optionAnswer": "A", "answer": " ", "optionB": "RSA", "type": "1", "optionA": "MD5", "knowledge": "\u52a0\u5bc6", "question": "Which of the following method(s) CANNOT be used for Text-encryption:", "title": "Microsoft-2014\u6821\u56ed\u62db\u8058\u7b14\u8bd5\u9898"}, {"ID": "55fa6a5ce4b043d0caf27237", "typeID": "55dd5e2360b258078b9e4458", "optionD": "Many clustered index", "optionC": "clustered index and many non-clustered indexes", "optionAnswer": "D", "answer": " ", "optionB": "A clustered index", "type": "1", "optionA": "No indexes", "knowledge": "\u6570\u636e\u5e93", "question": "A table CANNOT have one or more of the following index configurations.", "title": "Microsoft-2014\u6821\u56ed\u62db\u8058\u7b14\u8bd5\u9898"}, {"ID": "55fa6a5ce4b043d0caf27238", "typeID": "55dd5e2360b258078b9e4458", "optionD": "1", "optionC": "0", "optionAnswer": "B", "answer": " ", "optionB": "-1", "type": "1", "optionA": "-2", "knowledge": "\u7f16\u7a0b\u57fa\u7840", "question": "Initialize integer i as 0, what's the value of i after the following operation?  i += i > 0 ? i++ : i --;  ", "title": "Microsoft-2014\u6821\u56ed\u62db\u8058\u7b14\u8bd5\u9898"}, {"ID": "55fa6a5ce4b043d0caf27239", "typeID": "55dd5e2360b258078b9e4458", "optionD": "BSS segment", "optionC": "global variable", "optionAnswer": "A", "answer": " ", "optionB": "static variable", "type": "1", "optionA": "code segment", "knowledge": "\u8fdb\u7a0b", "question": "When a dll is loaded into memory, which part(s) can be shared between processes", "title": "Microsoft-2014\u6821\u56ed\u62db\u8058\u7b14\u8bd5\u9898"}, {"ID": "55fa6a5ce4b043d0caf2723a", "typeID": "55dd5e2360b258078b9e4458", "optionD": "O(n*n)", "optionC": "O(nlgn)", "optionAnswer": "C", "answer": " ", "optionB": "O(n)", "type": "1", "optionA": "O(lgn)", "knowledge": "\u590d\u6742\u5ea6", "question": "The best time complexity of quick sort algorithm is:", "title": "Microsoft-2014\u6821\u56ed\u62db\u8058\u7b14\u8bd5\u9898"}]}